# **JOSUÉ DE LA CRUZ**

OR: JOSHISADESIGNER

Find some of my work at

https://joshisadesigner.github.io

linkedin.com/in/joshisadesigner joshisadesigner@me.com +502 5052-8589

### Statement

Motivated and experienced Graphic Designer and Web Developer with 12 and 7 years experience, respectively. I like to put my experience, effort, and abundant creativity into building notable websites, making use of my Design, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript knowledge.

#### Skills

5 5 8	♦ Ps Ai Id Ŵ
Front-End:	HTML, CSS, JavaScript,
Design:	Sass, Bootstrap Figma, Invision, Sketch Photoshop, Illustrator,
Tools:	Indesign Command Line, Git, Github, Gitlab, BitBucket
Language skills	
Spanish: English:	

#### Education

2017 to 2018

Front-End Web Developer

Udacity Nanodegree

2002 to 2014

Bachelor's Degree in Multimedia Graphic Design

Universidad San Carlos De Guatemala

2000 to 2001

Computer Certificate with Scientific Guidance

Liceo Roca de Ayuda

## Work experience

August 2016 to Date **UI/UX Designer and Web Developer** Secure IP, Guatemala.

June 2016 to September 2017 **Konsus Design Specialist** Konsus, Inc, Remote.

June 2015 to August 2016

UI/UX Designer and Web Developer
ssnapp part of Social Media Gateways, Inc.,
Guatemala.

From October 2014 to June 2015 **UI/UX Designer and Web Developer** XYZ Network, Guatemala.

January 2009 to October 2014

**UI/UX Designer and Graphic Designer.**Unidad Creativa Independiente, Guatemala.

## Project experience

- Introduced CSS methodologies as SMACCS and BEM for americavoice.com Customer Portal and public websites.
- Improve the markup structure and CSS
   Bootstrap classes used in the America Voice

   Reseller Portal platform.
- I helped develop and organize CSS styles for StarMedia.com, LatinChat, LatinMail, and other brands making use of SASS and methodologies like SMACCS.
- Applied HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to solve several issues on applications to work responsively on a large range of devices for the ssnapp client platform.
- Achieve excellent feedback on customer improving ssnapp Front-End system.
- Seamlessly worked with Full Stack Developers.